Juan Ignacio Demaestri

Mechanical Engineer, MBA **Data Scientist**



+549 2346636942





https://github.com/jidemaestri



juanignaciodemaestri@gmail.com



SUMMARY

Mechanical Engineer (UTN Buenos Aires). Master of Business Administration (MBA)

5 years of experience in Project Management (+3 years in the Automotive Industry, currently in the Oil & Gas industry).

Main interests: Data Analysis, Finance, Automotive Ind., Technology. My objective is to work on challenging projects for the future, applying Data Science to these areas.

CAREER

SEP 2019 - PRESENT

TRADICOM ARGENTINA

Lead Project Engineer

- Training in Houston, TX in January 2020.
- · Focused on development and project planning. Contact and negotiation with suppliers and clients.

AUG 2017 - JUL 2019

MERCEDES-BENZ ARGENTINA

Project Engineer

- Management of Databases and operational data: Scoreboard and KPI. Analysis of Operational Processes.
- Assistance to the After-Sales Director (Latam) in planning the financial budget of the sector.
- SAP / Excel / ISO 14001 / ISO TS 16949.

FEB 2016 - AUG 2017

METALSA ARGENTINA

· Management of operational data.

Project Engineer Jr.

- Preparation of KPIs and scoreboards. Process Analysis.
- I have worked as a Jr Engineer in the Logistics and Supply Chain area assisting SR Engineers in the implementation of continuous improvement projects.

EDUCATION

2017-2020

UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL

Master of Business Administration (MBA)

• Specialization in Management & Finances

· Thesis Pending

• 8/10

2011 - 2017

UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL · Facultad Buenos Aires

Mechanical **Engineer**

Graduated in 2017, 7.91/10

SKILLS

Python (NumPy, Pandas, Scikit, MatPlotLib), TensorFlow, Statistics, Algebra, Data Visualization, Databases (MySQL), SAP, PowerBI, Excel.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH: Advanced - GERMAN: Basic

COURSES

Aplicaciones Mecánicas con Microcontroladores ARM (UTN) | Desarrollo en Python (Platzi) | Introducción a Machine Learning (Platzi) | Inyección Electrónica en Motores de Combustión (UTN) | Machine Learning y Redes Neuronales con Python (Udemy) | Pentair Filtration Systems - Oil & Gas